Well, I think my favorite word, and I think this is something I say always, for everything and for nothing, for everything, for nothing, and because it's always thank you.
Because I think that when you thank any person for any gesture they make, not only for you, but for the universe, for life.
When you give that thanks, besides being grateful, you're giving encouragement and you're motivating that action to happen again.
When you see a person sweeping the street, those people who do the public cleaning,
those people are ignored by everyone.
But when you thank one of those people and you see the smile on their face,
knowing that street is clean with a lot of love.
So I think saying thank you everywhere,
knowing how to say thank you in any language, is something very important,
my favorite word. Thank you very much.